digital marketing



Education:

- ~BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY-B.TECH
- ~MASTER OF TECHNOLOGY- M.TECH
- ~BACHELOR OF EDUCATION- B.ED
- ~CERTIFICATION IN DIGITAL MARKETING

INTEGRAL UNIVERSITY-INDIA PERCENTAGE-75% (HONORS)

Skill:

I possess a diverse set of skills including Client Relationship Management, Clinical Research and Clinical Operations, Business Development, Blog Writing. Creative Writing, Content Writing. Research and Development, Market Research, Digital Marketing, Online Marketing, Corporate Sales, B2B Sales, Medical Devices, Medical Sales, Laboratory Skills, B2B Sales and Marketing. **Email** Marketing, Social Media Marketing, Google AdWords, SEO, Infographics, Canva Designing, WordPress, Marketing Strategy, **Affiliate** Inbound Marketing, Marketing, Advertising, Google Analytics, **Ecommerce** Marketing, and Reputation Management.

About Me:

I have a strong background in marketing, sales, digital marketing, social media marketing, client relationship management and mangement. I am confident in my ability to contribute effectively to your team. Enclosed is which further outlines resume, experiences and achievements. I would welcome the opportunity to discuss how my background, skills, and enthusiasms can be aligned with the goals of your company. Thank you for considering my application. I look forward to the possibility of contributing to your team and learning more about the exciting work being done at your company.

Experience:

FREELANCER Multiple Brands

2023-2024

As a freelancer for one year, I specialized in digital marketing, social media marketing, and content creation, managing end-to-end campaigns for various clients across multiple industries. I developed targeted social media strategies, created engaging content, and optimized online presence through SEO and paid ad campaigns. My work included crafting compelling blog posts, social media copy, and multimedia content, alongside analyzing performance metrics to improve engagement and ROI. I successfully helped clients grow their brands, increase web traffic, and strengthen their digital footprint.

HEAD OF MARKETING AND RESEARCH

2021-2023

International Technical Legacy-Qatar

Results-driven professional in **Digital Marketing**, **Marketing**, **Sales**, **Corporate Sales**, and **Business Development**. Worked in market research, brand positioning, and content creation, contributing to a 20% rise in brand awareness and customer engagement.

CONTENT MANAGER

2020-2021

The school Matters, Chegg, Digital magazine

MARKETING MANAGER

2015-2020

Navdrishti and Sons Pvt Ltd-India

Developed and implemented marketing strategies across email, content, and social media platforms, driving an increase in brand awareness. Managed content creation for blogs, email newsletters, and social media, leading to increase in user engagement.

Coordinated promotional events and product launches, improving customer acquisition.